On the blue summer evenings,
I shall go down the paths,
Getting pricked by the corn,
crushing the short grass:
In a dream I shall feel
its coolness on my feet.
I shall let the wind
bathe my bare head.
I shall not speak,
I shall think about nothing:
But endless love
will mount in my soul;
And I shall travel far,
very far, like a gipsy,
Through the countryside
- as happy as if I were with a woman.
On the blue summer evenings,
I shall not speak,
I shall go down the paths,
I shall think about nothing:
Getting pricked by the corn,
But endless love
crushing the short grass:
will mount in my soul;
In a dream I shall feel
And I shall travel far,
its coolness on my feet.
very far, like a gipsy,
I shall let the wind
Through the countryside
bathe my bare head.
- as happy as if I were with a woman.